Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Images of Yale individuals
1745-2001
RU 684
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
78.67
The materials consists of pictures of individuals associated with Yale, including students, faculty, officers, and visitors. Includes portrait photographs, and prints of drawings and paintings.
General note
This collection differs from RU 686, Photographs of individuals from the Yale University News Bureau, which strictly contains photographs maintained by the university for publicity purposes.
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The materials consists of pictures of individuals associated with Yale, including students, faculty, officers, and visitors. Includes portrait photographs, and prints of drawings and paintings.
Arrangement
The images are arranged in two series and subsequent accessions. I. Alphabetical list of individuals. II. Oversize.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Accession 2015-A-056 is gift of George C. Anderheggen, 2015.
Drawings (visual works); Engravings (prints); Photographs; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Faculty; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Officers and employees; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Officers and employees; Yale University -- Students
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Aaron, Lewis B. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbe, E. H. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, F. F. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Gardner (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abbott, James Whiting (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abbott, Josiah (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Mather Almon (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Montelius (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abbott, Wilbur Cortez (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aber, William Martin (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aborn, Carlton Nisbet (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acheson, Dean (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ackerman, George C. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ackley, Oliver Sidney (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acosta, John Sidney (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Albert Egerton (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Alva Blanchard (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Charles Edward (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, C. F. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, Charles Francis (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adams, Francis F. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adams, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adams, Frederick Blanchard (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, George E. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, George Washington (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, James Truslow (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, John (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adams, Norman I., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adams, Thatcher Magoun (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, Thatcher Magoun (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, Thomas Sewall (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, W. A. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adams, Whittlesey (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adams, William (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adams, William Jr. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Adams, ???? (Prof.) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adee, Augustus A. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adee, George A. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adee, George T. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adler, Frederick Max (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Afong, Chun Wing Sen (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aghajanian, Dr. George K. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aiken, William Pope (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Aikens, Claude G. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Akerlof, G. C. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Albelli, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Albin, George Waugh (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alden, David Root (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Aldrich, C.F. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aldrich, Malcolm P. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aldrich, Richard S. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aldrich, Thomas Bailey (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alexander, Eben (1873) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alexander, Ira R. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Alexander, William De Witt (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Algase, Charles G. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alger, Hugh W. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Allen, Arthur Dwight (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Allen, Rev. Arthur H (1873) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Allen, C. W. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Allen, Charles James Fox (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Allen, Clarence Emir, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Allen, Edgar (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Allen, Edmund Thompson (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Allen, Edwin Lee (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Allen, Frank D. (1873) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Allen, G. Walter (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Allen, George William (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Allen, Grosvenor Noyes (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Allen, John De Witt Hamilton (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Allen, Oscar D. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Allen, Philip Ray (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Allen, Samuel Evan Stokes (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Allen, Walter (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Allen, William Seward (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Allerton, George Milton (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alling, Arthur W. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Alling, John W. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Allis, Wallace Steel (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Allison, John M. S. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Almy, Leonard B. (1873) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Alofsin, Elihu H. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Alofsin, Frederick Benjamin (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Alsop, Richard (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Alvord, Edward Jesup (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Alvord, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Alvord, Robert Williams (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Ambler, R. C. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ames, Anthony (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ames, F. E. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ames, Paul K. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Ames, Sullivan D. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Amis, Reese T. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Anderson, E. Clay (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Anderson, Ernest Arthur (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Anderson, Joshua (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Anderson, Robert (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Anderson, Volney Stamps (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Anderson, William D. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Anderson, William G. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Andre, John (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Andrew, George (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Andrew, Samuel (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Andrews, Charles M. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Andrews, Donald H. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Andrews, Ebenezer (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Andrews, Ethan Allen (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Andrews, Frank Van Dyke (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Andrews, George Pierce (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Andrews, James Brown (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, John Wallingford (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, John Williams (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andrews, John Wolcott (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Andrews, Joseph Hyde (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Andrews, Judson Boardman (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Andrews, Launcelot Winchester (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Andrews, Leon Hudson (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Andrus, Hamlin Forster (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Angell, James Rowland (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Photos (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Portraits (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Snapshots (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Photos with Charles Seymour (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Group photos (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Commencement photos (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Photos of grave in Grove Street Cemetery (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Angier, Roswell Parker (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Angleton, James J. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Anketell, John Henry (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Anway, Wilmore (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Appleton, Robert (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Apter, David E. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Arbuthnot, Charles (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Arbuthnot, Thomas S. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Archbald, Robert Wodrow (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Archbald, Thomas Frothingham (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Archer, ? (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Arcolarius, Pidu B. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Armour, C (Prof) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Arms, Charles J. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Arms, William F. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Armsby, Henry Prentiss (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Armstrong, Arthur H. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Armstrong, George Humphrey (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Armstrong, George Leslie (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Armstrong, Richard (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Armstrong, William N. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Arnold, George Waterman (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Arnold, Hubbard (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Arnold, Thurman (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Arnold, William (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Arnot, John Hulett (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Arons, Milton (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Arthur, William P. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Asbury, Herbert (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Ashburn, Frank D. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Ashe, William W. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Asher, Abraham (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Ashley, Clarence Degrand (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Ashmun, George (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Aspin, Leslie, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Atherton, George W. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Atherton, Harlan E. (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Atkins, Paul Moody (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Atterbury, William Wallace (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Atwater, Isaac (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Atwater, William M. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Atwood, James (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Auchincloss, James C. (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Augur, George J. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Augur, Robert Clayton (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Austin, Archibald Alexander (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Averell, William Holt (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Avery, Charles Hammond (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Avery, Frederick D. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Ayers, Charles R. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Ayres, Charles (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Ayres, Frank Oliver (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Ayres, Philip W. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Babb, James Tinham (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Babbitt, Theodore (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Babcock, George (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Babcock, Col. Henry (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Babcock, Henry H. (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Bache, Alexander Dallas (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bachman, Archer Wayland (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Bachman, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Backus, Azel (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Backus, Joseph W. (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Backus, William Henry (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Backus, William Warner (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bacon, Asa (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bacon, Charles (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bacon, David (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Bacon, Epaphroditus Champion (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bacon, Francis (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Bacon, Leonard (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Bacon, Theodore (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Bacon, Theodore C. (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Bacon, Thomas Rutherford (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bacon, William Plumb (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Bacon, William T. (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Badger, George Edmund (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Badger, Samuel Augustus (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Badham, Henry Lee, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Baer, Benjamin F. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Baer, Sidney R. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bagg, Lyman (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Bail, Louis (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Bailey, B (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bailey, Adolphe (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bailey, Edward (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Bailey, Marge (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Bailey, Mark (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Bailey, Parker (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Bailey, Stephen Goodhue (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Bailey, William L. (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Baird, George William (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Baird, John Gunn (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Baird, John Taylor (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Baird, Lucius Olmsted (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Baker, Alanson Judson (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Baker, Frederick S. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Baker, Prof. George P. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Baker, Harris Walton (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Baker, Hugh Potter (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Bakewell, Charles M. (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Baldridge, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Baldwin, Abraham (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Baldwin, Charles Sears (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Baldwin, Charles Winterfield (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Baldwin, Edward Robinson (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Baldwin, Frank Lee (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Baldwin, George William (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Baldwin, Henry (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Baldwin, Henry (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Baldwin, Henry P. (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Baldwin, Louis Whittier (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Baldwin, R. S. (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Baldwin, Samuel E. (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Baldwin, Simeon (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Baldwin, Simeon Eben (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Baldwin, William Pitt (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Ball, William W. (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Ballou, Earle E. (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Bancroft, Cecil Franklin Patch (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Banghart, Harold L. (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Bangs, Francis H. (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Bankowsky, R. J. (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Banks, Charles R. (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Banks, George W. (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Banks, L. Maxwell (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Bannan, Douglas Ridgeway (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Bannan, John Newell (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Bannard, Otto Tremont (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Barber, John M. (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Barber, Maurice Compton (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Barber, Walter Lewis (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Barber, William (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Barbour, Frank (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Barbour, the Rev"d Dr (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Barclay, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Barclay, Thomas Dougall (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bard, Prof. Erwin W. (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Bardon, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Bardwell, Robert Daniel, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Barhydt, Steele (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Barickman, Richard (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Barker, George Frederick (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Barlow, Joel (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Barlow, J. B. (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Barnaby, Kenneth Tuttle (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Barnard, Frederick A. P. (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Barnard, Frederick J. (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Barnard, Henry (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Barnes, Bayard (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Barnes, Clifford Webster (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Barnes, Courtland Dixon (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Barnes, Henry Burr (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Barnes, Henry B., Jr. (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Barnes, Henry Weldon (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Barnes, Jonathan (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Barnes, T. Cunliff (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Barnes, William Samuel (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Barnett, Paul (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Barnett, J. G. (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Barnum, Burrall (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Barnum, Henry S. (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Barnum, Samuel Weed (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Barnum, William Milo (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Barrett, Charles H. (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Barrett, Myron (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Barrows, Edwin (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Bartholomew, Harold B. (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Bartholomew, Marshall (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Bartlett, Charles Leffingwell (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Bartlett, Evans E. (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Bartlett, Nathaniel (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Bartlett, Samuel Colcord (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Bartlett, William Frederick Vincent (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Bartlett, William N. (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Barton, Albert Raymond (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Bartram, Rensselaer Wardwell (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Bass, George E. (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Batchelor, E. P. (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Bates, Carlos (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Bates, Isaac Chapman (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Bates, William L. (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Bates, Xyris S. (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Battell, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Battershall, Walton Wesley (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Baxter, Hamilton (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Bayne Jones, Stanhope & Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Beach, John Kimberly (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Beach, Joseph Wickliff (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Beach, Thomas Belknap (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Beadle, Delos White (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Beadle, Heber H. (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Beale, Robert M. (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Beals, Pascall Pratt (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Bean, David M. (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Bean, Perry William (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Beane, Alpheus Crosby, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Beard, Augustus F. (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Beard, George Miller (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Beardsley, Alonzo Gover (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Beardsley, C. R. (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Beardsley, Dan (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Beardsley, Monroe Curtis (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Beardsley, Nelson (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Beardsley, William Porter (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Beck, Frederick George (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Beck, Margaret (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Becket, G. Campbell (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Beckwith, Brainerd Kellogg (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Beckwith, Nathan Edward (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Becton, Henry P. (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Bedell, Bradbury (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Bedell, Frederick (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Beebe, Lucius (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Beebe, Roderick (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Beebe, William (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Beecher, Charles Emerson (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Beecher, Edward (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Beecher, George Buckingham (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Beecher, Harry (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Beecher, Henry Ward (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Beecher, Luther F. (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Beecher, Lyman (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Beecher, Victor (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Beekman, Joe (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Beers, Clifford Whittingham (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Behr, Karl Howell (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Beers, Henry A. [?] (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Beers, William Cooke (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Behrisch, Gabriel Isidore (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Behrman, Morris Harry (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Beinecke Brothers (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Belcher, Moses T. (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Belden, Joseph Congdon (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Belden, William Henry (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Beldine, John Eastman (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Belin, Henry (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Belin, Paul Beck (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Bell, Goodloe Bowman (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Bellamy, Joseph H. (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Bellinger, Louisa (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Bement, Edward (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Benavente, Senor (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Bench, E. C. (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Bendelari, Prof. (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Benet, Lawrence (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Benham, H. W. (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Benham, Harry (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Benjamin, C. E. (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Benjamin, Hamilton Fish (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Benjamin, Joseph Ritner (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Benjamin, Judah Philip (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Benner, Charles (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Benner, Willis (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Bennett, George K. (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Bennett, Henry Silliman (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Bennett, Jones Russell (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Bennett, Stephen Alexander (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Bennett, Thomas G. (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Bennitt, Chandler (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Bensinger, Allan R. (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Benson, Frank Sherman (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Benson, J. William (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Bent, Samuel Arthur (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Bentley, George F. (1873) (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Bentley, W. H. (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Benton, Fred (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Berg, Charles F (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Bergen, Frank (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Bergen, Henry Vanderveer (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Berger, Charles William (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Berger, George B., Jr. (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Bergin, Thomas (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Berkele, Elmer Fox (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Berkeley, Bishop George (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Bernstein, Richard J. (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Berry, Coburn Dewees (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Besley, Fred (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Besley, Lowell (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Best, John Walter (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Betts, Edward Richmond (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Betts, Jackson E. (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Betts, Samuel Rossiter (Box 5, Folder 179-181)
  - Bezjiian, Alexander (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Bickel, Alexander M. (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Biddle, Alfred Alexander (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Biddle, Algernon (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Biddle, George W. (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Biddle, Henry J. (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Biddle, Julian Cornell (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Bidell, Charles E. (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Bidwell, Walter Hillard (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Biebuyck, Daniel P. (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Bierworth, John Edward (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Bigelow, Albert (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Bigelow, C. W. (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Bigelow, David Skinner (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Bigelow, Frank (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Bigelow, Lucius Aurelius (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Bigelow, Nelson Pendleton (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Bigelow, Poultney (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Bilheimer, Robert Sperry (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Bill, Charles (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Billings, Edward Coke (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Bingham, Alfred Mitchell (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Bingham, Charles William (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Bingham, Egbert B. (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Bingham, Hiram II (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Bingham, Hiram III (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Bingham, Hiram IV (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Bingham, Joel Foote (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Bingham, Robert Harold (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Bingham, Theodore Alfred (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Binkley, Clark (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Bird, Charles Willard (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Bird, Howard (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Bird, Isaac (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Bird, James (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Birdseye, Lucien (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Birnie, Thomas Noyes (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Bishop, Albert Webb (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Bishop, Avard L. (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Bishop, Edward G. (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Bishop, Fred M. (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Bishop, Henry A. (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Bishop, John H. (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Bishop, Julian Brocklehurst (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Bishop, William Darius (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Bishop, William Henry (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Bissell, Alfred (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Bissell, Clark (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Bissell, Edward (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Bissell, George Perkins (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Bissell, Hugh M. (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Bissell, Johnathan Edwards (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Bissell, William Church (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Bissell, William (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Bissell, William T. (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bissell, Wilson Shannon (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bitterworth, Frank S. (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bittker, Boris Irving (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Bixler, G. Fordham (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Black, Charles L. (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Black, Willis James (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Black, William Ross (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Blackman, John H., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Blackman, Samuel Curtis (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Blackstock, Walter (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Blackwell (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Blaine, Walker (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Blair, Burton Dickinson (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Blair, Edwin Foster (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Blair, Watson K. (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Blair, Wiley, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Blake, Edward Foster (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Blake, Eli Whitney (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Blake, James Pierpont (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Blake, William Phipps (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Blakeslee, Clarence (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Blakeslee, Erastus (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Blakeslee, Henry Clay (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Blakesley, Linus (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Blaney (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Blatchford, C. H. (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Blatchley, Charles C. (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Blatchley, Samuel R. (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Bliss, Charles Franklin (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Bliss, Charles Miller (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Bliss, Edwin Munsell (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Bliss, George (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Bliss, Henry I. (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Bliss, L. (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Blodgett, George Reddington (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Bloom, Harvey H. (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Bloomer, J. R. (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Blossom, John T. (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Blount, Archibald H. (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Blum, Alexander (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Blum, John (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Blumenthal, Andre (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Boardman, Bradford (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Boardman, Dixon (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Boardman, Herbert (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Bockee, Jacob S. (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Bogel, Rick (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Bogue, Samuel Russell (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Bohan, Charles Patrick (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Boies, Charles Alfred (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Boies, Henry Matin (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Boies, Henry Whiting (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Boies, William (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Boies, William E1y (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Bolton, Frances Mary (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Boltwood, Bertram B. (Box 6, Folder 231)